<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addons>
<addon id="repository.yellowdragon" name="Yellow Dragon Repository" version="17.7" provider-name="YLLOW_DRAGON">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Yellow Dragon Repository">
        <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nkvoronov/repository.yellowdragon/krypton/repo/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nkvoronov/repository.yellowdragon/krypton/repo/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nkvoronov/repository.yellowdragon/krypton/repo/</datadir>
        <hashes>false</hashes>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">YLLOW_DRAGON addons repository for KODI Krypton</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Репозиторий плагинов YLLOW_DRAGON для KODI Krypton</summary>
        <description  lang="en">Download and install YLLOW_DRAGON addons repository.</description>
        <description  lang="ru">Загружайте и устанавливайте плагины из репозитория YLLOW_DRAGON.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <news></news>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.yellowdragon.ext" name="Yellow Dragon Repository Ext" version="17.7" provider-name="YLLOW_DRAGON">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Yellow Dragon Repository Ext">
        <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nkvoronov/repository.yellowdragon.ext/krypton/repo/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nkvoronov/repository.yellowdragon.ext/krypton/repo/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nkvoronov/repository.yellowdragon.ext/krypton/repo/</datadir>
        <hashes>false</hashes>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">YLLOW_DRAGON EXT addons repository for KODI Krypton</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Репозиторий плагинов YLLOW_DRAGON EXT для KODI Krypton</summary>
        <description  lang="en">Download and install YLLOW_DRAGON EXT addons repository.</description>
        <description  lang="ru">Загружайте и устанавливайте плагины из репозитория YLLOW_DRAGON EXT.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <news></news>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.busyspinners.estuary" name="Animated Busy Spinners Pack Estuary" version="1.0.1.001" provider-name="marcelveldt, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="false" type="busyspinners" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Animated Busy Spinners Pack - Estuary</summary>
		<description lang="en">Animated Busy Spinners Pack - Estuary</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
        <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/resource.images.busyspinners.estuary</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.skinicons.estuary" name="Skin Icons - Estuary" version="1.0.0.001" provider-name="YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="false" type="skinicons" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Skin Icons Pack - Estuary</summary>
		<description lang="en">Skin Icons Pack - Estuary</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
        <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/resource.images.skinicons.estuary</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.cu.lrclyrics" name="CU LRC Lyrics" version="5.5.5.011" provider-name="Taxigps, ronie, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.chardet" version="2.2.1"/>
		<import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.3.2"/>
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.18.4"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.lyrics" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="default.py" start="login"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="be_BY">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">CU LRC Лирики</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">CU LRC-Songtext</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Στίχοι CU LRC</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Paroles CU LRC</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Letras de CU LRC</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">CU LRC tekstovi pjesama</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">CU LRC Dalszöveg</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Lirik CU LRC</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">CU LRC dainų žodžiai</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">CU LRC songteksten</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">CU LRC sangtekster</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">CU LRC Letras</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Versuri CU LRC</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="sl_SI">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">CU LRC Lyrics</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">CU LRC Lyrics 歌词插件</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">CU LRC Lyrics 歌詞腳本</summary>
		<description lang="be_BY">CU LRC Lyrics is a lyrics script for Kodi. It supports regular as well as LRC Lyrics. The script can search synchronized/unsynchronized lyrics embedded, from file or by scrapers. It can read .lrc/.txt lyrics file saved at the same path by same file name with .mp3(or other type of music).</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">CU LRC Лирики е добавка за лирики. Поддържа обикновени текстови файлове и .lrc файлове. Може да търси за синхронизирани/несинхронизирани лирики вградени в аудиофайловете или да ги извлича от различни източници. Може да прочита .lrc и .txt файлове съхраняващи лирики, които се намират в папката на дадения аудио файл (с разширение .mp3 например) и носят неговото име.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">CU LRC Lyrics es un script de lletres de cançons per a Kodi. Suporta lletres normal tan com LRC Lyrics. El script busca lletres sincronitzades o no, incrustades al fitxer d'àudio, des de un altre fitxer o per scrapers. Pot llegir fitxers .lrc/.txt guardats al mateix directori i nom de fitxer amb .mp3(o un altre tipus de música).</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">CU LRC Lyrics er et script til sangtekster til Kodi. Det understøtter almindelige såvel som LRC sangtekster. Script'et kan søge i synkroniserede/usynkroniserede sangtekster som er inkodede i filer eller ved hjælp af scrapere. Det kan læse .lrc/.txt sangtekstfiler som er gemt i den samme mappe og med samme filnavn som mp3'en (eller andre typer af musikfiler).</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">CU LRC-Songtext ist ein Songtextskript für Kodi, das sowohl normale als auch LRC-Songtexte unterstützt. Das Skript kann nach synchronisierten/unsynchronisierten eingebetteten Songtexten von Datei oder Scraper suchen. Es kann .lrc/.txt-Songtextdateien lesen, die im gleichen Pfad und mit dem gleichen Dateinamen mit .mp3 (oder eine anderen Musikart) gespeichert wurden.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Οι Στίχοι CU LRC είναι ένα script στίχων για το Kodi. Υποστηρίζει συνηθισμένους στίχους καθώς και Στίχους LRC. Το script μπορεί να αναζητήσει συγχρονισμένους και μη στίχους, ενσωματωμένους, από αρχεία ή από scraper. Μπορεί να διαβάσει αρχεία στίχων τύπου .lrc/.txt που βρίσκονται στον ίδιο φάκελο και έχουν το ίδιο όνομα με το .mp3 (ή άλλης κατάληξης μουσική).</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">CU LRC Lyrics is a lyrics script for Kodi. It supports regular as well as LRC Lyrics. The script can search synchronized/unsynchronized lyrics embedded, from file or by scrapers. It can read .lrc/.txt lyrics file saved at the same path by same file name with .mp3(or other type of music).</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">CU LRC Lyrics is a lyrics script for Kodi. It supports regular as well as LRC Lyrics. The script can search synchronised/unsynchronised lyrics embedded, from file or by scrapers. It can read .lrc/.txt lyrics file saved at the same path by same file name with .mp3(or other type of music).</description>
		<description lang="en_US">CU LRC Lyrics is a lyrics script for Kodi. It supports regular as well as LRC Lyrics. The script can search synchronized/unsynchronized lyrics embedded, from file or by scrapers. It can read .lrc/.txt lyrics file saved at the same path by same file name with .mp3(or other type of music).</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">CU LRC Lyrics es un script de letras para Kodi. Es compatible tanto con letra regular como LRC Lyrics. El script puede buscar desde archivo o a través de scrapers letras incrustadas sincronizadas o no sincronizadas. Puede leer archivos .lrc/.txt guardados en la misma carpeta con el mismo nombre del archivo *.mp3 (u otro tipo de archivo de audio).</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">CU LRC Lyrics est un script pour gérer les paroles dans Kodi. Il supporte les formats de paroles habituels aussi bien que LRC. Le script peut chercher des paroles synchronisées/désynchronisées intégrées dans les fichier ou par collecteurs. Il peut lire les fichiers paroles .lrc/.txt stockés dans le même dossier et avec le même nom que le fichier .mp3 (ou autre type de format musical).</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Paroles CU LRC est un script de paroles pour Kodi. Il prend en charge les paroles régulières et LRC. Le script peut rechercher des paroles synchronisées/désynchronisées intégrées, d'un fichier ou de récupérateurs. Il peut lire les fichiers de paroles .lrc/.txt enregistrés dans le même chemin et avec le me nom que le .mp3 (ou autres types de musique).</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Letras CU LRC é un script de letras para Kodi. Soporta letras normais como as LRC. O script pode buscar letras sincronizadas/non sincronizadas incrustadas, ou buscar a partir dun ficheiro ou de scrapers. Pode ler letras de ficheiros .lrc/.txt gardados na mesma ruta do ficheiro .mp3 (ou outro tipo de música).</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">CU LRC Lyrics הינו סקריפט מילות שירים עבור Kodi התומך בפורמט LRC והן בטקסט רגיל. הסקריפט מסוגל לחפש מילות שיר מסונכרות/לא מסונכרות המוטמעות בשיר, מקובץ מקומי או בעזרת סקרייפר. הסקריפט מסוגל לקרוא קובץ מילות שיר txt/lrc השמור באותו נתיב עם שם זהה לקובץ ה-mp3 (או סוג אחר של קובץ מוזיקה).</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">CU LRC tekstovi pjesama je skripta za Kodi. Podržavna redovne i LRC tekstove pjesama. Skripta može pretraživati usklađivati/uklanjati ugrađene tekstove pjesama, iz datoteke ili sakupljača. Može čitati .lrc/.txt datoteke tekstova pjesama spremljene u istu putanju s istim nazivom datoteke sa .mp3 (ili drugim vrstama glazbe).</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">A CU LRC Dalszöveg egy kiegészítő az Kodi-hez, ami támogatja  a hagyományos és az LRC dalszövegek keresését, megjelenítését. A dalszöveg lehet szinkronizált, vagy szinkronizálatlan, a zenefájlba beágyazott, vagy leolvasókkal letöltött, vagy akár származhat a zene könyvtárában található .lrc vagy .txt fájlokból is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Lirik CU LRC adalah script lirik untuk Kodi. Mendukung lirik regular maupun LRC. Script ini mampu mencari lirik dengan singkronisasi maupun tidak yang tercantum pada berkas atau melalui alat penyalin. Script dapat membaca berkas lirik .lrc/.txt yang disimpan di lokasi dan nama berkas yang sama dengan .mp3 (atau format musik lainnya).</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">CU LRC Lyrics è uno script per i testi per Kodi. Supporta testi come LRC. Lo script può cercare testi incorporati sincronizzati e non, da file o tramite scapers. Legge file .lrc/.txt salvati nello stesso percorso e con lo stesso nome dell'.mp3 (o altri tipi di musica)</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">CU LRC Lyrics는 Kodi를 위한 가사 수집기입니다. 일반 가사와 LRC 가사를 지원하며, 내장 가동기/비동기 가사를 검색하거나 파일 내장 가사를 찾습니다. mp3(또는 다른 형식의 음악 파일)와 같은 경로에 저장되어 있는 .lrc/.txt 형식의 가사를 읽어옵니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">CU LRC Lyrics yra dainų žodžių atsiuntimo skriptas, skirtas Kodi. Palaikomi tiek įprasti, tiek LRC dainų žodžiai. Skriptas gali ieškoti sinchronizuotų / nesinchronizuotų dainų žodžių, integruotų failuose arba naudojant skreperius. Jis gali nuskaityti .lrc/.txt dainų žodžių failus, išsaugotus toje pačioje vietoje ir tokiu pačiu pavadinimu kaip ir .mp3 failas (ar kitokio muzikinio failo tipo).</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">CU LRC Lyrics is een script voor songteksten in Kodi. Het ondersteunt zowel reguliere als LRC songteksten. Het script ondersteunt gesynchroniseerde of ongesynchroniseerde songteksten die ingebed zijn in een bestand, in een los bestand staan of van een scraper. Het kan .lrc/.txt songtekst-bestanden lezen die opgeslagen zijn op hetzelfde pad en dezelfde bestandsnaam hebben als de .mp3 (of ander type bestand).</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">CU LRC Lyrics er et skript for å vise sangtekster i Kodi. Den støtter vanlige samt LRC sangtekster. Skriptet kan søke synkroniserte / usynkroniserte sangtekster innebygd, fra en fil eller via skrapere. Den kan lese .lrc / .txt filer som er lagret på den samme banen og med samme filnavn (.mp3 eller annen type musikk).</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">CU LRC Lyrics jest dodatkiem obsługującym teksty utworów dla Kodi. Obsługuje teksty utworów zarówno zwykłe jak i zsynchronizowane. Dodatek potrafi wyszukać teksty zapisane lokalnie, wbudowane w pliki utworów, a także pobierać je z Internetu. Potrafi wczytać teksty w formatach .lrc/.txt zapisane w tym samym folderze co pliku utworu .mp3 (lub innym wspierany formacie).</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">CU LRC Lyrics é um script de letras para o Kodi. Suporta letras normais e LRC. O script pode encontrar letras sincronizadas/dessincronizadas embutidas, ou procurar a partir de ficheiro ou de colectores. Pode ler letras de ficheiros .lrc/.txt guardados na mesma localização do ficheiro .mp3 (ou outro tipo de música).</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">CU LRC Lyrics é script de letras de músicas para Kodi. Ele suporta regular bem como Letras LRC. O script pode procurar por letras embutidas sincronizadas/dessincronizadas, de arquivos ou usando scrapers. Ele pode ler arquivos de letras .lrc/txt salvos no mesmo caminho com o mesmo nome do arquivo .mp3 (ou outro formato de música).</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">CU LRC Lyrics je doplnok poskytujúci texty skladieb pre Kodi. Podporuje bežné ako aj LRC formáty. Doplnok môže vyhľadávať synchronizované/nesynchronizované Texty skladieb vložené, v samostatnom súbore alebo cez sťahovače. Dokáže čítať .lrc/.txt súbory v rovnakom priečinku a s rovnakým názvom ako .mp3 súbor (alebo iný hudobný súbor).</description>
		<description lang="sl_SI">CU LRC Lyrics je skripta za besedila pesmi za Kodi. Podpira redne kot tudi LRC besedila pesmi. Skripta lahko išče sinhronizirana/nesinhronizirana besedila pesmi, vgrajena, iz datoteke ali od ponudnikov. Bere lahko .lrc/.txt formate zapisa datotek iz iste mape kot je istoimenska datoteka .mp3 (ali drigi format zapisa glasbe).</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">CU LRC Lyrics är ett skript för Kodi. Det stödjer såväl vanliga som LRC texter. Skriptet kan söka synkroniserade/osynkroniserade texter inbäddade från fil eller från skraport. Det kan läsa .lrc/.txt filer sparade med samma sökväg och filnamn som .mp3 (eller annan typ av musik).</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">CU LRC Lyrics 是 Kodi 的歌词插件。它支持原 LRC Lyrics 歌词插件的功能。这个插件会搜索内嵌的、本地文件或通过刮削器获取同步/非同步歌词。它可以读取以相同文件名与歌曲文件保存在相同目录的 .lrc/.txt 歌词文件。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">CU LRC Lyrics 是為 Kodi 而設的歌詞腳本。它支援一般格式的歌詞以及 LRC 格式的歌詞。此腳本能夠搜尋歌曲檔案內嵌歌詞的同步及非同步歌詞，同時也能使用刮削器在線搜尋、本地文件或通过刮削器获取同步/非同步歌词。它可以讀取放在同一個資料夾內，而又與歌曲相同命名的 .lrc/.txt 歌詞檔。</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=147340</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.cu.lrclyrics/</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon
	id="script.epg.vsetv"
	name="Vse TV"
	version="3.0.3"
	provider-name="YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">VsёTV - TV Program, movie trailers, TV shows, sports</summary>
		<summary lang="ru">ВсёТВ - Телепрограмма, анонсы фильмов, сериалы, спорт</summary>
		<description lang="en">VsёTV 2.0 - more than 650 channels of TV Program in Ukraine, Russia, Europe, the announcements of all the movies, TV shows, sports on TV, news TV, the largest catalog of serials, the ability to customize a set of channels and the format of information delivery</description>
		<description lang="ru">ВсёТВ 2.0 - Телепрограмма более 650 каналов Украины, России, Европы, анонсы всех фильмов, сериалов, спорт на ТВ, новости телевидения, крупнейший каталог сериалов, возможность настроить под себя набор каналов и формат выдачи информации</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.epg.vsetv.git</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.favourites" name="Favourites script" version="7.1.1" provider-name="ronie, `Black">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="be_BY">Favourites script</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Скрипт "Любими"</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Script Preferit</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Script pro Oblíbené</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Favoritscript</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Favoriten-Skript</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Script Αγαπημένων</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Favourites script</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Favourites script</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Favorites script</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Script de Favoritos</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Favoritos</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Suosikit skripti</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Script Favoris</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Le script des favoris</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Script de Favoritos</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">סקריפט מועדפים</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Omiljene skripte</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Kedvencek script</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Script favorit</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Script preferiti</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">즐겨찾기 스크립트</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Mėgstamiausių skriptas</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Favourietenscript</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Favorittskript</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skrypt ulubionych</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Script de Favoritos</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Script Favoritos</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Script Favorite</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Скрипт "Избранное"</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Favoritskript</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Sık kullanılanlar betiği</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">收藏夹脚本</summary>
		<description lang="be_BY">Fetches item from your Kodi favourites to populate Home menu/submenu with custom buttons.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Извлича информация от вашето меню "Любими" и показва допълнителни бутони в главното меню и подменюто.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Obtenir els temes Preferits dels seus Kodi per omplir el menú Inici / submenú amb botons personalitzats.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Přenese položky z Oblíbených do Home menu/submenu pod vlastní tlačítka. </description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Henter elementer fra din Kodi-favoritter til at fylde Hjemmemenu/undermenu med brugerbestemte knapper.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Stellt die Einträge aus der Kodi-Favoriten-Liste für benutzerdefinierte Verknüpfungen auf dem Startbildschirm zur Verfügung.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Χρησιμοποιεί αντικείμενα από τα αγαπημένα σας του Kodi για να συμπληρώσει τα προσαρμοσμένα πλήκτρα μενού/υπομενού της Αρχικής Οθόνης</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Fetches item from your Kodi favourites to populate Home menu/submenu with custom buttons.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Fetches item from your Kodi favourites to populate Home menu/submenu with custom buttons.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Fetches item from your Kodi favorites to populate Home menu/submenu with custom buttons.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Usar ítems de tus favoritos de Kodi para crear menús y submenús personalizados</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Obtiene medios de sus favoritos en Kodi para enriquecer su menu inicio y sub carpetas con botones personalizados</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Hakee Kodin suosikeista kohteita ja populoi sillä Koti-valikon / alivalikon muokatuilla napeilla.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Récupère l'élément depuis les favoris Kodi pour remplir le menu/sous-menu de la page d'accueil avec des boutons personnalisés.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Récupère l'élément de vos favoris Kodi pour remplir le menu d'accueil/le sous-menu avec des boutons personnalisés.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Obtén o elemento dos favoritos para estabelecer botóns personalizados no Menú Principal/Submenú</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">מייבא פריט מהמועדפים שלך לאכלוס תפריט/תת תפריט עם לחצנים מותאמים אישית במסך הבית.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Dohvaća stavke iz vašeg Kodi 'Omiljeno' izbornika i popunjava Početni izbornik/podizbornik s prilagođenim tipkama.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Összegyűjti az elemeket az Kodi kedvencek közül és a központi menü almenüjébe helyezi egyedi gombokkal.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Ambil item dari favorit Kodi Anda untuk mengisi menu/submenu Beranda dengan tombol suka-suka.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Preleva elementi dai tuoi preferiti per popolare il menù principale ed i sottomenù con bottoni personalizzato.</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Kodi 즐겨찾기에서 항목을 가져와 사용자 설정 버튼으로 홈 메뉴/서브메뉴에 표시합니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Paima elementus iš Kodi mėgstamiausiųjų, kad užpildytų pagrindinio meniu/submeniu individualiais mygtukais.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Haalt item van je Kodi favorieten op om in het Home menu/submenu te plaatsen via losse buttons.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Henter oppføringer fra favorittene dine i Kodi for å befolke hovedmenyen og undermenyen med egendefinerte knapper.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Pobiera pozycje z twoich ulubionych w celu zapełnienia menu/podmenu niestandardowymi przyciskami.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">Obtém itens dos seus favoritos do Kodi para povoar o Menu Principal/submenu com botões personalizados.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Compila itens dos seus favoritos do Kodi para ocupar menus e submenus da tela inicial com botões personalizados.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Извлекает информацию из Вашего меню "Избранное" и отображает дополнительные кнопки в главном меню и подменю.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Hämtar objekt från dina Kodi-favoriter för att fylla ut hem-menyn med egna knappar.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">将 Kodi 收藏夹项目用于主界面菜单/子菜单的自定义按钮。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Needs skin support for it to be used properly</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Необходима е поддръжка от страна на облика за коректно функциониране</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Necessita Suport de la pell perquè sigui utilitzat correctament</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Pro správné použití je potřeba podpora skinu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Behøver skinsupport for at blive brugt ordentligt</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Benötigt Skin-Support um korrekt genutzt zu werden</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Απαιτείται υποστήριξη από το κέλυφος για να χρησιμοποιηθεί σωστά</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Needs skin support for it to be used properly</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Needs skin support for it to be used properly</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Needs skin support for it to be used properly</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Necesita ser soportado por el skin para poder funcionar correctamente</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Necesita soporte de mascara para ser usada correctamente</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Toimiakseen kunnolla, skinin tulee tukea tätä</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Nécessite le support du thème pour qu'il soit utilisé correctement</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Le prise en charge de l'habillage est nécessaire pour qu'il soit utilisé correctement</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Precisa da axuda da pel para que sexa utilizado correctamente</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">להפעלה כראוי נדרשת תמיכה במעטפת</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Zahtijeva podršku presvlake za ispravno korištenje</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Felszín támogatás szükséges a helyes működéshez</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Memerlukan dukungan kulit untuk dapat digunakan dengan baik</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">E' necessario che lo skin supporti lo script per funzionare correttamente</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">스킨에서 지원해야 합니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Reikalingas teminės išvaizdos palaikymas tinkamam naudojimui</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Heeft skinondersteuning nodig om correct te werken</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Krever skallstøtte for å fungere riktig</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Wymagane wsparcie skórki w celu poprawnego działania</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">Necessita de um tema compatível para funcionar correctamente.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Necessita de suporte da skin para ser usado adequadamente</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Necesită suport din partea costumului pentru a fi folosit cum trebuie</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Необходима поддержка скинов для корректного отображения</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sl_SI">Potrebuje podporo preobleke, da bo uporabljeno pravilno.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Behöver skalsupport för att kunna användas riktigt</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Düzgün kullanılabilmesi için dış görünüm desteğine ihtiyacınız var</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">正常使用需要皮肤支持</disclaimer>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=114671</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email></email>
		<source>https://github.com/ronie/script.favourites</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.globalsearch" name="Global Search" version="7.4.7.005" provider-name="ronie, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="bg">Търси в библиотеката Ви.</summary>
		<summary lang="ca">Cerca a la teva biblioteca.</summary>
		<summary lang="cs">Hledej v knihovně</summary>
		<summary lang="de">Durchsuchen Sie Ihre Bibliothek.</summary>
		<summary lang="el">Αναζήτηση στη Συλλογή σας.</summary>
		<summary lang="en">Search your library.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Search your library.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Search your library.</summary>
		<summary lang="es">Busca tu biblioteca.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr">Chercher dans la médiathèque.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Chercher dans votre bibliothèque</summary>
		<summary lang="gl">Buscar a súa biblioteca.</summary>
		<summary lang="he">חיפוש בספריית המדיה.</summary>
		<summary lang="hr">Pretražite svoju zbirku.</summary>
		<summary lang="hu">Keresés a médiatárban</summary>
		<summary lang="id">Cari pustaka Anda.</summary>
		<summary lang="it">Ricerca nella la tua libreria.</summary>
		<summary lang="ko">라이브러리 찾기</summary>
		<summary lang="lt">Ieškoti bibliotekoje.</summary>
		<summary lang="nl">Zoek in je bibliotheek.</summary>
		<summary lang="no">Søk i biblioteket ditt</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">Przeszukaj swoją bibliotekę</summary>
		<summary lang="pt">Faça buscas na sua biblioteca.</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Pesquise sua coleção.</summary>
		<summary lang="ro">Căutați în mediateca dumneavoastră.</summary>
		<summary lang="ru">Поиск в вашей медиатеке.</summary>
		<summary lang="sl">Iščite v svoji knjižnici.</summary>
		<summary lang="sv">Sök i ditt bibliotek.</summary>
		<summary lang="tr">Kitaplığını ara</summary>
		<summary lang="zh">资料库搜索</summary>
		<description lang="bg">Добавката може да намери всеки елемент във вашата видео и музикална библиотека.</description>
		<description lang="ca">Aquest complement pot trobat qualsevol article en la teva biblioteca de vídeo i música</description>
		<description lang="cs">Tento dopněk dokáže najít libovolnou položku ve vaší audio a video knihovně.</description>
		<description lang="de">Dieses Add-on kann jeden Eintrag in Ihrer Video- und Musikbibliothek finden.</description>
		<description lang="el">Αυτό το πρόσθετο μπορεί να βρει κάθε αντικείμενο στις συλλογές σας.</description>
		<description lang="en">This addon can find any item in your video and music library.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">This addon can find any item in your video and music library.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">This addon can find any item in your video and music library.</description>
		<description lang="es">Este complemento puede encontrar cualquier elemento en tu biblioteca de vídeo y música.</description>
		<description lang="fr">Cette extension peut trouver tout élément dans la vidéothèque et l'audiothèque.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Cet addiciel peut trouver tout élément dans votre vidéothèque et dans votre audiothèque.</description>
		<description lang="gl">Este complemento pode atopar calquera elemento na súa biblioteca de medios.</description>
		<description lang="he">הרחבה זו יכולה למצוא כל פריט בספריות הווידאו והמוזיקה.</description>
		<description lang="hr">Ovaj dodatak može pronaći svaku stavku u vašoj videoteci ili fonoteci.</description>
		<description lang="hu">Ez a kiegészítő bármely elemet megtalálja a videó és audió médiatárban.</description>
		<description lang="id">Addon ini dapat mencari item apa saja di pustaka video dan musik Anda.</description>
		<description lang="it">Questo addon può trovare ogni elemento nella tua libreria video ed in quella musicale.</description>
		<description lang="ko">비디오와 음악 라이브러리의 모든 항목을 검색합니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt">Šis priedas gali rasti bet kokį elementą jūsų vaizdo ir garso bibliotekoje.</description>
		<description lang="nl">Deze addon kan elk item in je video- en muziekbibliotheken vinden.</description>
		<description lang="no">Dette tillegget kan finne hva som helst i ditt film eller musikk bibliotek.</description>
		<description lang="pl">Ten plugin może odnaleźć dowolną pozycję w twojej bibliotece wideo oraz muzycznej.</description>
		<description lang="pt">Este addon pode encontrar qualquer item na sua biblioteca de vídeos e de músicas.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Este addon pode encontrar qualquer item na sua coleção de vídeos e música.</description>
		<description lang="ro">Acest supliment poate găsi orice element în mediateca dumneavoastră video și audio.</description>
		<description lang="ru">Это дополнение поможет найти любую запись в вашей медиатеке.</description>
		<description lang="sl">Ta dodatek lahko poišče katerokoli podatek v vaši knjižnici filmov in glasbe.</description>
		<description lang="sv">Detta tillägg kan hitta vilket objekt som helst i ditt video och musikbibliotek.</description>
		<description lang="tr">Bu eklenti video ve müzik kitaplığınızdaki herhangi bir öğeyi bulabilir.</description>
		<description lang="zh">此插件搜索你的视频和音乐资料库项目。</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=109301</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.globalsearch.git</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.image.resource.select" name="Image Resource Select Addon" version="2.0.2.004" provider-name="ronie, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Image resource selection addon</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Выбор дополнения ресурса изображения</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Script for skinners to let users select an image resource addon.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Скрипт позволяет пользователям выбрать дополнение ресурса изображения.</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=239558</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.image.resource.select.git</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.cherrypy"
       name="CherryPy Kodi module"
       version="11.0.1.002"
       provider-name="marcelveldt, CherryPy Team, YLLOW_DRAGON">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.9.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">CherryPy webserver packaged as Kodi module</summary>
        <summary lang="ru_RU">Веб-сервер CherryPy, упакованный как модуль Kodi</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">CherryPy is a pythonic, object-oriented web framework
            CherryPy allows developers to build web applications in much the same way they would build any other object-oriented Python program. This results in smaller source code developed in less time.
            CherryPy is now more than ten years old and it is has proven to be very fast and stable. It is being used in production by many sites, from the simplest to the most demanding.
        </description>
        <description lang="ru_RU">CherryPy - это питоновая, объектно-ориентированная веб-структура
             CherryPy позволяет разработчикам создавать веб-приложения почти так же, как и для любой другой объектно-ориентированной программы Python. Это приводит к меньшему исходному коду, разработанному за меньшее время.
             Теперь CherryPy более десяти лет, и это оказалось очень быстрым и стабильным. Он используется в производстве на многих сайтах, от самых простых до самых требовательных.
        </description>
        <license>BSD</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.module.cherrypy.git</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.metadatautils"
		name="Metadata and Artwork module"
		version="1.0.19.017"
		provider-name="marcelveldt, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.3.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8" />
		<import addon="script.module.thetvdb" version="0.0.1" />
		<import addon="script.module.musicbrainz" version="0.0.1" />
		<import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.arrow" version="0.6.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Metadata and artwork from common sources TMDB, IMDB and fanart.tv </summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Метаданные и иллюстраций из общих источников TMDb, IMDB и fanart.tv </summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">The artwork and metadata module provides rich metadata, including artwork for various metatypes by scraping this information from sites like TMDB, musicbrainz and fanart.tv.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Модуль artwork and metadata получает метаданные и иллюстраций для различные метатипов с сайтов TMDb, MusicBrainz и fanart.tv.</description>
		<license>Apache 2.0</license>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.module.metadatautils.git</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.musicbrainz"
       name="Musicbrainz NGS webservice python bindings"
       version="0.6.0.002"
       provider-name="marcelveldt, YLLOW_DRAGON">
  <requires>
  <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Python bindings for Musicbrainz' NGS webservice</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Python модуль для вебсервиса Musicbrainzngs</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Kodi module library for the Python bindings for Musicbrainz' NGS webservice developed by alastair.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Kodi Python модуль для вебсервиса Musicbrainzngs, разработанного alastair.</description>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</license>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
    <source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.module.simplecache.git</source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.simplecache" name="Simple Cache Module" version="1.0.16.008" provider-name="marcelveldt, YLLOW_DRAGON">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Provides a simple file- and memory based cache for Kodi addons</summary>
        <summary lang="ru_RU">Предоставляет простой файл на основе кэш-памяти для KODI дополнений</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Provides a simple file- and memory based cache for Kodi addons</description>
        <description lang="ru_RU">Предоставляет простой файл на основе кэш-памяти для KODI дополнений</description>
        <license>Apache 2.0</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.module.simplecache.git</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.thetvdb"
       name="The TVDB API v2"
       version="1.0.27.010"
       provider-name="marcelveldt, YLLOW_DRAGON">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.3.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.arrow" version="0.6.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">TheTVDB API v2 python module for Kodi</summary>
        <summary lang="ru_RU">TheTVDB API v2 модуль python для Kodi</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">TheTVDB API v2 python module for Kodi</description>
        <description lang="ru_RU">TheTVDB API v2 модуль python для Kodi</description>
        <license>Apache 2.0</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
        <source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.module.thetvdb.git</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id='script.module.torrent.ts' version='0.7.3.5.001' name='AceStream client' provider-name='1orgar, YLLOW_DRAGON'>
	<requires>
		<import addon='xbmc.python' version='2.7.8'/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
	<extension point='xbmc.addon.metadata'>
		<summary>AceStream client</summary>
		<platform>all</platform>
        <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
        <source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.module.torrent.ts.git</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon
    id="script.pvr.favourites"
    name="PVR favourites"
    version="2.0.9"
    provider-name="YLLOW_DRAGON">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.20.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.unidecode" version="0.4.14"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="default.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <description lang="en">It gets information about PVR channels and displays additional buttons and widgets on the main menu and submenus.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">Skins support needed for correct display.</disclaimer>
        <description lang="ru">Получает информацию об PVR каналах и отображает дополнительные кнопки и виджеты в главном меню и подменю.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="ru">Необходима поддержка скинов для корректного отображения.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
        <source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.pvr.favourites.git</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.randomandlastitems" name="Random and Last items script" version="2.2.2.002" provider-name="MikeBZH44, Martijn, Black, YLLOW_DRAGON">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
        <import addon="xbmc.json" version="6.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="randomandlastitems.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Random And Last Items script</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">Random And Last Items script</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Скрипт - случайные и последние элементы </summary>
        <description lang="en">Script to get Random or Last added movies, episodes, albums or music videos from the database.Can optionnaly handle playlist to filter results.</description>
        <description lang="fr">Script qui retourne, soit de manière aléatoire, soit les derniers ajouts, les films, épisodes, albums ou clips de la base de données.Il peut optionnellement gerer les playlistes pour filtrer les resultats.</description>
        <description lang="ru">Скрипт получает случайное или последние добавленные фильмы, эпизоды, альбомы или музыкальные клипы из медиатеки. Может обрабатывать плейлист для фильтрации результатов.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
        <website></website>
        <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=122448</forum>
        <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
        <source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.randomandlastitems.git</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.rss.editor"
       name="RSS Editor"
       version="3.0.2.003"
       provider-name="rwparris2, Team Kodi, YLLOW_DRAGON">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script"
             library="default.py" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en">A Script for editing Kodi's built in RSS Ticker</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">RSS forrás szerkesztő</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Skript zum Bearbeiten des Kodi internen RSS Tickers</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Скрипт для редактирования бегущей строки RSS KODI</summary>
    <description lang="en">A Script for editing Kodi's built in RSS Ticker</description>
    <description lang="hu">A szkript képes szerkeszteni az Kodi beépített RSS forrás készletét</description>
    <description lang="de">Skript zum Bearbeiten des Kodi internen RSS Tickers</description>
    <description lang="ru">Скрипт для редактирования бегущей строки RSS KODI</description>
    <language></language>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website></website>
    <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
    <source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.rss.editor.git</source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.simpleplaylists"
    name="SimplePlaylists"
    version="1.1.1.003"
    provider-name="AddonScriptorDE, YLLOW_DRAGON">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video audio image</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Add local media (video/audio/images) and add-on content to playlists while browsing/watching your media. To use this addon you have to map the following command to a key: "RunPlugin(plugin://script.simpleplaylists/?mode=addCurrentUrl)". More Info: forum.xbmc.org</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Добавляйте локальное медиа (видео/аудио/изображения) и контент дополнений в плейлисты во время просмотра медиатеки. Для использования этого плагина вы должны выполнить следующую команду: "RunPlugin(plugin://script.simpleplaylists/?mode=addCurrentUrl)". Дополнительная информация: forum.xbmc.org</summary>
        <description lang="en">Add local media (video/audio/images) and add-on content to playlists while browsing/watching your media. To use this addon you have to map the following command to a key: "RunPlugin(plugin://script.simpleplaylists/?mode=addCurrentUrl)". More Info: forum.xbmc.org</description>
        <description lang="ru">Добавляйте локальное медиа (видео/аудио/изображения) и контент дополнений в плейлисты во время просмотра медиатеки. Для использования этого плагина вы должны выполнить следующую команду: "RunPlugin(plugin://script.simpleplaylists/?mode=addCurrentUrl)". Дополнительная информация: forum.xbmc.org</description>
        <language></language>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
        <source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.simpleplaylists.git</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

	<addon id="script.skin.helper.backgrounds" name="Skin Helper Service Backgrounds" version="1.0.33.017" provider-name="marcelveldt, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.13.0"/>
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.pil" version="1.1.7"/>
		<import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.metadatautils" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="default.py" />
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Helper service for Kodi skins providing rotating backgrounds</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Сервис помощник для KODI обложек (Фоны)</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">>Helper service for Kodi skins providing rotating backgrounds</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Сервис помощник для KODI обложек (Фоны)</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL v2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=235676</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.skin.helper.backgrounds.git</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

	<addon id="script.skin.helper.colorpicker" name="Skin Helper Service ColorPicker" version="1.0.12.009" provider-name="marcelveldt, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.pil" version="1.1.7"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="default.py" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Colorpicker for Kodi Skins. Part of Skin Helper Suite</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Выбор цвета для обложки KODI. Часть Skin Helper</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Colorpicker for Kodi Skins. Part of Skin Helper Suite</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Выбор цвета для обложки KODI. Часть Skin Helper</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL v2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=235676</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.skin.helper.colorpicker.git</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

	<addon id="script.skin.helper.service" name="Skin Helper Service" version="1.1.24.030" provider-name="marcelveldt, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.13.0"/>
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.metadatautils" version="1.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.cherrypy" version="11.0.0"/>
	</requires>

	<extension point="kodi.context.item">
		<menu id="kodi.core.main">
			<item library="resources\lib\context_animatedart.py">
			  <label>32024</label>
			  <visible>!IsEmpty(Window(Home).Property(SkinHelper.EnableAnimatedPosters)) + Container.Content(movies)</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="resources\lib\context_pvr.py">
				<label>32023</label>
				<description>PVR artwork Configuration</description>
				<visible>
					!IsEmpty(Window(Home).Property(SkinHelper.EnablePvrThumbs)) +
					[Window.IsActive(MyPVRChannels.xml) |
					Window.IsActive(MyPVRGuide.xml) | Window.IsActive(MyPVRRecordings.xml) |
					Window.IsActive(MyPVRTimers.xml) | Window.IsActive(MyPVRSearch.xml)]
				</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="resources\lib\context_music.py">
				<label>32023</label>
				<description>Music artwork Configuration</description>
				<visible>
					!IsEmpty(Window(Home).Property(SkinHelper.EnableMusicArt)) +
					[Container.Content(albums) | Container.Content(artists) | Container.Content(songs)]
				</visible>
			</item>
		</menu>
	</extension>

	<extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="default.py" />
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py">
	</extension>
	<extension library="service.py" point="xbmc.service" start="login" />

	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Helper service for Kodi skins</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Сервис помощник для KODI обложек</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Helper service for Kodi skins</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Сервис помощник для KODI обложек</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL v2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=235676</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.skin.helper.service.git</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

	<addon id="script.skin.helper.skinbackup" name="Skin Helper Service Skin Backup" version="1.0.19.014" provider-name="marcelveldt, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.13.0"/>
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py" />
	<extension library="service.py" point="xbmc.service" start="login" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Helper service for Kodi skins (Backup)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Сервис помощник для KODI обложек (Резерное копирование)</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Helper service for Kodi skins (Backup)</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Сервис помощник для KODI обложек (Резерное копирование)</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL v2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=235676</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.skin.helper.skinbackup.git</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

	<addon id="script.skin.helper.widgets" name="Skin Helper Service Widgets" version="1.0.38.022" provider-name="marcelveldt, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.metadatautils" version="1.0.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py">
		<provides>video audio</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension library="service.py" point="xbmc.service" start="login" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Ready to use widgets for all kind of media types</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Готовые к использованию виджеты для всех типов медиа-типов</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Ready to use widgets for all kind of media types</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Готовые к использованию виджеты для всех типов медиа-типов</description>
		<description></description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL v2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=235676</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.skin.helper.widgets.git</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.skinshortcuts" name="Skin Shortcuts" version="1.0.18.019" provider-name="BigNoid, marcelveldt, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.20.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.unidecode" version="0.4.14"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<news>Template improvements and bug fixes</news>
		<description lang="bg">Добавка за облици, която осигурява просто управление и списък с потребителски преки пътища (изисква поддръжка от облика)</description>
		<description lang="de">Add-on für Skins für einfache Bearbeitung und Auflistung von benutzerdefinierten Verknüpfungen (erfordert Skin-Unterstützung)</description>
		<description lang="el">Πρόσθετο για κελύφη, το οποίο παρέχει έναν απλό τρόπο διαχείρισης και κατηγοριοποίησης των συντομεύσεων του χρήστη (πρέπει να υποστηρίζεται από το κέλυφος)</description>
		<description lang="en">Add-on for skins to provide simple managing and listing of user shortcuts (requires skin support)</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Add-on for skins to provide simple managing and listing of user shortcuts (requires skin support)</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Add-on for skins to provide simple managing and listing of user shortcuts (requires skin support)</description>
		<description lang="es">Complemento para las pieles para proporcionar una gestión sencilla y lista de atajos de usuario (requiere que la piel lo soporte)</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Addiciel pour habillages qui fournit une gestion simple et un listage des raccourcis utilisateurs (exige la prise en charge de l'habillage)</description>
		<description lang="gl">Complemento que fornece aos temas dunha xestión sinxela dos atallos dos usuarios (require soporte do tema)</description>
		<description lang="hr">Dodatak za presvlake koja omogućava jednostavno upravljanje i prikaz korisnikovih prečaca (zahtijeva podršku presvlake) </description>
		<description lang="hu">Felszín kiegészítő amely könnyen kezelhetővé és listázhatóvá teszi a felhasználói parancsikonokat (Felszín támogatás szükséges)</description>
		<description lang="is">Viðbót fyrir viðmót til að halda utan um flýtivísa og fá yfirlit yfir þá (þarfnast stuðnings frá viðmóti)</description>
		<description lang="it">Add-on per gli skin per consentire un facile gestione ed elenco delle scorciatoie utente (richiede che lo skin lo supporti)</description>
		<description lang="lt">Priedas teminėms išvaizdoms, kad jos turėtų galimybę paprastai tvarkyti ir atvaizduoti vartotojo  sukurtas nuorodas (reikalingas teminės išvaizdos palaikymas)</description>
		<description lang="nl">Add-on voor skins om te voorzien in het eenvoudig beheren en sorteren van gebruikers snelkoppelingen (vereist skin ondersteuning)</description>
		<description lang="no">Tillegg for enkel administrering og opplisting av bruker-snarveier i tema (krever støtte i tema)</description>
		<description lang="pl">Wtyczka dla skór, która zapewnia proste zarządzanie i tworzenie list skrótów użytkownika (wymaga wsparcia skóry)</description>
		<description lang="pt">Um add-on que permite que os temas tenham recursos simples para gerir e listar atalhos de utilizadores (é necessário suporte do tema)</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Add-on para que as skins possam prover gerenciamento de lista de atalhos para o menu principal (requer suporte da skin)</description>
		<description lang="ru">Дополнение для обложек, предоставляющее простой способ управления списками пользовательских ярлыков (требуется поддержка обложкой)</description>
		<description lang="sv">Skinntillägg som tillhandahåller enkel hantering och översikt av användargenvägar (om skinnet stöder det)</description>
		<description lang="zh">插件为皮肤提供了简单的管理和用户连接方式列表 (需要皮肤支持)</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU General Public License, v2</license>
		<forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=178294</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.skinshortcuts.git</source>
	<assets>
		<icon>icon.png</icon>
		<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
	</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.transmission"
    name="Transmission"
    version="0.7.6.001"
    provider-name="Correl Roush, YLLOW_DRAGON">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8" />
        <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.5.2" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/player.py" start="startup"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">A client for the popular Transmission BitTorrent application</summary>
        <summary lang="hu">A népszerű Transmission Bittorrent alkalmazás vezérlése</summary>
        <summary lang="ca">Un client de Transmission, la popular aplicació de Bittorrent</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Клиент для популярного приложения BitTorrent</summary>
        <description lang="en">Currently, Transmission-XBMC supports viewing, adding, removing, starting and stopping torrents. More advanced features may be added in future releases.</description>
        <description lang="hu">Jelenleg a Transmission-XBMC képes megnézni, hozzáadni, elkezdeni, és megállítani a torrenteket. További fejlesztések várhatók a jövőben.</description>
        <description lang="ca">Actualment, Transmission-XBMC permet veure, afegir, eliminar, iniciar i parar torrents. En futures versions de l'aplicació s'haniran afegint opcions més avançades.</description>
        <description lang="ru">В настоящее время, Transmission-XBMC поддерживает просмотр, добавление, удаление, запуск и остановка торрентов. Более продвинутые функции могут быть добавлены в будущих версиях.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>MIT</license>
        <forum></forum>
        <website></website>
        <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
        <source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/Transmission-XBMC.git</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon
    id="script.vdr.front"
    name="Run VDR Fronend"
    version="1.1.2"
    provider-name="YLLOW_DRAGON">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script"  library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Start VDR frontend</summary>
        <description lang="en">Start VDR frontend</description>
        <summary lang="ru">Старт VDR frontend</summary>
        <description lang="ru">Старт VDR frontend</description>
        <platform>linux</platform>
        <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
        <source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.vdr.front.git</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.xbmc.audio.mixer"
    name="Kodi Audio Mixer"
    version="4.0.1.003"
    provider-name="Team Kodi, YLLOW_DRAGON">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>osx linux</platform>
        <summary lang="en">Kodi Audio Mixer</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Kodi Аудио Микшер</summary>
        <description lang="en">Kodi Audio Mixer</description>
        <description lang="ru">Kodi Аудио Микшер</description>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
        <forum></forum>
        <website></website>
        <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
        <source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/script.xbmc.audio.mixer.git</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.xbmc.lcdproc" name="XBMC LCDproc" version="2.6.0.003" provider-name="Team XBMC: Memphiz, Daniel 'herrnst' Scheller, YLLOW_DRAGON">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0"/>
        <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="lcdmain.py" start="login"></extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <language></language>
        <summary>XBMC LCDproc</summary>
        <description lang="en">Displays configurable information e.g. about playing media or XBMC status on any LC/VF-display driven by LCDproc, and acts as direct drop-in replacement to the LCD/VFD-feature previously available in XBMC's core. Supports additional display elements (icons, bars) on SoundGraph iMON LCD and Targa/Futaba mdm166a VFD hardware. Requires a properly configured and running LCDd either locally or somewhere on the network.</description>
        <description lang="ru">Отображает настраиваемую информацию, например, о воспроизводимом медиа или статус XBMC на любой LC/VF-дисплей который управляется LCDProc и действует как прямая замена к LCD/VFD--функции, ранее доступные в ядре XBMC. Поддерживает дополнительные элементы отображения (иконки, бары) на SoundGraph iMON LCD и Targa/Futaba mdm166a VFD аппаратного обеспечения. Требуется правильно сконфигурированый и запущенный LCDd либо локально, либо где-то в сети.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">Works with LCDproc only. Other LCD services like LCD4Linux or iMON Manager on Win32 are not supported. No liability taken for damaged hardware and/or software caused by this addon.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ru">Работает только с LCDProc. Другие LCD сервисы, такие как LCD4Linux или IMON менеджер для Win32 не поддерживаются. Никакая ответственность не принимается за поврежденного оборудования и/или программного обеспечения, вызванного этим аддоном.</disclaimer>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon
    id="service.3denabler.samsungtv"
    name="3D Enabler Samsung TV"
    version="0.1.1.001"
    provider-name="Pavel Kuzub, YLLOW_DRAGON">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="script.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <language/>
    <summary lang="en">Switch Samsung TV into 3D mode when playing 3D movie</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Переключение Samsung TV в режим 3D при проигрывании 3D фильма</summary>
    <description lang="en">Once you start your 3D movie - your Samsung 3DTV that is connected to your LAN should switch to respective 3D mode automatically</description>
    <description lang="ru">Как только вы начнете просмотр вашего 3D кино - ваш Samsung 3DTV, который подключен к вашей локальной сети, должен автоматически переключиться в соответсвующий 3D режим</description>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
    <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=185212</forum>
    <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
    <source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/service.3denabler.samsungtv.git</source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.skin.widgets" name="Skin Widgets" version="0.0.33.003" provider-name="Martijn, phil65, YLLOW_DRAGON">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.json" version="6.0.0"/>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="default.py" start="login"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="be">Skin widgets</summary>
        <summary lang="da">Widgets til Skins</summary>
        <summary lang="de">Skin Widgets</summary>
        <summary lang="el">Widgets κελύφους</summary>
        <summary lang="en">Skin widgets</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Skin widgets</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">Skin widgets</summary>
        <summary lang="gl">Widgets do Tema</summary>
        <summary lang="hr">Dodaci za presvlaku</summary>
        <summary lang="hu">Kinézet miniprogram</summary>
        <summary lang="it">Skin widgets</summary>
        <summary lang="ko">스킨 위젯</summary>
        <summary lang="nl">Skin widgets</summary>
        <summary lang="pl">Dodatki Skóry</summary>
        <summary lang="pt">Widgets para Temas</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Skin widgets</summary>
        <summary lang="sk">Widgety Vzhľadov</summary>
        <summary lang="sv">Skal widgetar</summary>
        <summary lang="zh">皮肤微件</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Виджеты обложки</summary>
        <description lang="be">Skin widgets</description>
        <description lang="da">Widgets til Skins</description>
        <description lang="de">Skin Widgets</description>
        <description lang="el">Widgets κελύφους</description>
        <description lang="en">Skin widgets</description>
        <description lang="es">Skin widgets</description>
        <description lang="fr">Skin widgets</description>
        <description lang="gl">Widgets do Tema</description>
        <description lang="hr">Dodaci za presvlaku</description>
        <description lang="hu">Kinézet miniprogram</description>
        <description lang="it">Skin widgets</description>
        <description lang="ko">스킨 위젯</description>
        <description lang="nl">Skin widgets</description>
        <description lang="pl">Dodatki Skóry</description>
        <description lang="pt">Widgets para Temas</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">Skin widgets</description>
        <description lang="sk">Widgety Vzhľadov</description>
        <description lang="sv">Skal widgetar</description>
        <description lang="zh">皮肤微件</description>
        <description lang="ru">Виджеты обложки</description>
        <disclaimer lang="be">For information visit the wiki page or XBMC forum.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="de">Besuche für mehr Informationen die Wiki-Seite oder das XBMC-Forum</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="el">Για πληροφορίες επισκεφθείτε τη σελίδα wiki ή το forum του XBMC.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en">For information visit the wiki page or XBMC forum.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es">Para más información, visite el wiki o los foros de XBMC.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr">Pour plus d'information, visitez la page du Wiki ou dur forum XBMC.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="gl">Para máis información visite a páxina wiki ou o foro do XBMC.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="hr">Za više informacija posjetite wiki stranicu ili XBMC forum.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="it">Per le informazioni visita la pagina wiki o il forum</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ko">위키 페이지나 XBMC 포럼에서 추가 정보를 확인하세요.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="nl">Bezoek voor informatie de wiki pagina of het XBMC forum.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pl">Odwiedź stronę wiki lub forum XBMC by znaleźć więcej informacji.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt">Para mais informação, visite a página wiki ou o fórum do XBMC.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Para informações visite o página do wiki ou fórum XBMC.org.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="sv">För information, besök wiki-sidan eller XBMC forumet.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="zh">访问wiki页或XBMC论坛了解更多信息</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ru">Для получения дополнительной информации посетите вики-страницу или XBMC форум.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
        <website></website>
        <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=142389</forum>
        <email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
        <source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/service.skin.widgets.git</source>
        <email></email>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon
	id="skin.confluence-extended"
	version="3.1.6.159"
	name="Confluence Extended"
	provider-name="Jezz_X, Team Kodi, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
		<import addon="script.image.resource.select" version="1.1.0"/>
		<import addon="script.favourites" version="6.0.3"/>
		<import addon="script.pvr.favourites" version="2.0.0"/>
		<import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.32"/>
		<import addon="script.randomandlastitems" version="2.2.2"/>
	</requires>
	<extension
		point="xbmc.gui.skin"
		defaultthemename="Textures.xbt"
		debugging="false"
		effectslowdown="1.0">
		<res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Confluence Extended oortreksel deur Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi se standaard tema)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">جلد "كونفليونس" من صنع Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (الجلد المبدأى لبرنامج إكس بى إم سى)</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Confluence Extended skin by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Confluence Extended облик от Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (стандартния облик за Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Confluence Extended, per Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Pell per defecte del Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Confluence Extended od Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cy_GB">Croen Confluence Extended gan Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Croen rhagosodedig Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Confluence Extended-tema af Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodis standardtema)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Confluence Extended Skin von Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Standard-Skin von Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Confluence Extended από τον Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="en_AU">Confluence Extended skin by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Confluence Extended skin by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Confluence Extended skin by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Confluence Extended skin by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Confluence Extended skin por Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Confluence Extended skin por Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (skin por defecto)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Skin confluende por Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Confluence Extended rüü autorilt Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Confluence Extended azala Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood egina.</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوسته Confluence Extended تهیه شده بوسیله Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (پوسته پیش فرض Kodi) </summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Confluence Extended-ulkoasu. Tekijä Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="fo_FO">Confluence Extended útsjónd av Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's vanliga útsjónd)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Confluence Extended par Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Thème Confluence Extended par Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Habillage d'origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Confluence Extended por Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">המעטפת Confluence Extended של Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (ברירת המחדל של Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Confluence Extended presvlaka autora Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (uobičajena Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Confluence Extended felszín. Készítő: Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="hy_AM">''Confluence Extended'' - տեսք՝ Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. կողմից (Kodi - հիմնական տեսք)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Confluence Extended oleh Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Skin bawaan Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Confluence Extended eftir Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Confluence Extended da Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Confluence Extended スキン by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">Confluence Extended 스킨 Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood 만듦 (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Confluence Extended teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi numatytoji teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Confluence Extended apvalks no Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi noklusētais apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Confluence Extended skin by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Penyatuan, kulit daripada Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="mt_MT">Dehra Confluence Extended magħmula minn Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Id-dehra normali ta' Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Confluence Extended-skall av Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodis standardskall)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Confluence Extended skin door Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's standaard skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Confluence Extended autorstwa Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Confluence Extended por Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Tema Confluence Extended por Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood (tema padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Costum Confluence Extended de Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (costum implicit pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Confluence Extended. Авторы: Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Confluence Extended skin od Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (predvolený skin Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sl_SI">Preobleka Confluence Extended avtorja Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Privzeta preobleka za Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sq_AL">Maska Confluence Extended nga Jazz_X (maska kryesore së Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Confluence Extended маска аутора Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Confluence Extended maska autora Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Confluence Extended, ett skal av Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi:s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Confluence Extended zrychtowanŏ ôd Jeez_X. (wychodnŏ skōra we Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tg_TJ">Пӯсти ҳамҷараёнӣ аз ҷониби Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Пӯсти пешфарзи Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">ชุดตกแต่ง Confluence Extended โดย  Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood (สกินเริ่มต้นของ Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Confluence Extended dış görünümü. Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood (Kodi'nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Confluence Extended. Автори: Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Confluence Extended bởi Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood 开发的 Confluence Extended 皮肤。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood 製作的佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Confluence Extended is die standaard oortreksel vir Kodi 14.0 en op. Dit is 'n kombinasie van konsepte van 'n klomp gewilde oortreksels, en 'n poging om hulle goeie idees te omvat en te integreer in 'n oortreksel wat maklik behoort te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">"كونفليونس" هو الجلد المبدأى لبرنامج إكس بى إم سى اﻹصدار 9.11 وما فوق. هو خلط بين اشهر اﻷجلده الاخرى معاً ومحاوله لتبنى ودمج افكارهم للخروج بِنِتَاج يُفترض به ان يكون سهل اﻹستيعاب بمجرد النظر لمستخدمى إكس بى إم سى المبتدئين.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Confluence Extended is the default skin for Kodi 14.0 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Confluence Extended е стандартният облик на Kodi 14.0 и по-новите версии. Представлява смесица от концепциите на много от популярните облици. Целта е да се интегрират тези добри идеи в подходящ и удобен вид за хора, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Confluence Extended és la pell per defecte del Kodi 14.0 i superiors. És una combinació de conceptes de moltes pells populars que intenta adoptar i integrar les seves bones idees en una aparença que sigui senzilla d'entendre i utilitzar per els nous usuaris de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Confluence Extended je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 14.0 a novější. Jedná se o kombinaci konceptů z mnoha jiných populárních vzhledů, která se pokouší uchopit a integrovat jejich dobré nápady do vzhledu, který by měl být pro nového uživatele Kodi jednoduchý na pochopení a používání.</description>
		<description lang="cy_GB">Confluence Extended yw croen rhagosodedig Kodi 14.0 ac uwch. Mae'n gyfuniad o gysyniadau o nifer o grwyn poblogaidd ac mae'n ymdrechu i gyfuno eu syniadau da hwy i groen ddylai fod yn hawdd i ddefnyddiwr cyntaf Kodi ei deall a'i ddefnyddio.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Confluence Extended er standardskin'et til Kodi 14.0 og senere versioner. Det er en kombination af koncepter fra mange populære skins, og det forsøger at omfavne og integrere de gode ideer i et skin, der er let for førstegangsbrugere af Kodi at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Confluence Extended ist der Standardskin ab Kodi 14.0. Er ist eine Kombination mehrerer unterschiedlicher Skin-Konzepte und versucht dabei, die besten Ideen zu kombinieren, um einen einfachen Einstieg für neue Kodi-Nutzer zu ermöglichen.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Confluence Extended είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 14.0 και άνω. Είναι ένας συνδυασμός από πολλές δημοφιλής αμφιέσεις, και επιχειρεί να παρέχει τις καλύτερες ιδέες τους σε μία αμφίεση, το οποίο είναι εύκολο για τους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi να κατανοήσουν και να χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_AU">Confluence Extended is the modernized skin for KODI. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Confluence Extended is the modernized skin for KODI. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Confluence Extended is the modernized skin for KODI. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Confluence Extended is the modernized skin for KODI. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Confluence Extended es el skin por defecto de Kodi 14.0 y posteriores. Es una combinación de conceptos de muchos skins populares, e intenta abarcar e integrar lo mejor de ellos en un skin que sea sencillo de entender y utilizar para los nuevos usuarios de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Confluence Extended es la skin por defecto de Kodi 14.0 y posteriores. Es una combinación de conceptos de muchas skins populares, e intenta abarcar e integrar lo mejor de ellas en una skin que sea sencilla de entender y utilizar para los nuevos usuarios de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Confluence Extended es el skin por defecto para Kodi 14.0 en adelante. Es una combinación de conceptos de varias skins populares, e intenta adoptar e integrar sus buenas ideas en un skin que debería ser fá de entender y usar para quienes usen Kodi por primera vez.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Confluence Extended on Kodi vaikerüü alates versioonist 14.0. Confluence Extended on paljude populaarsete rüüde kombinatsioon, üritades omavahel siduda nende parimaid lahendusi, et saavutada esmakasutajale selget ja kergelt kasutatavat tulemust.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Confluence Extended hainbat azal ospetsutatik hartutako kontzeptuen konbinaketa da. Horietatik ideia onak hartu eta integratzen saiatzen da, Kodi lehen aldiz erabiltzen dutenentzat ulertzeko eta erabiltzeko erraza izango den azal batean.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">Confluence Extended پوسته پیش فرض Kodi در ویرایش 14 و بالاتر است. این پوسته ترکیبی از چند پوسته محبوب دیگر است و تلاش دارد بهترین ایده ها را با هم ترکیب کند، تا شروعی ساده و آسان را برای کاربران جدید Kodi امکان پذیر سازد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Confluence Extended on yhdistelmä useiden suosittujen ulkoasujen konsepteista, ja yritys omaksua ja integroida heidän hyvät ideat ulkoasuun, jonka pitäisi olla helppokäyttöinen ja -tajuinen kaikille Kodin käyttäjille.</description>
		<description lang="fo_FO">Confluence Extended er vanliga útsjóndin, sum er brúkt í Kodi síðan útg. 14.0. Hetta er ein samansjóðan av fleiri hugtøkum. Ætlanin er at útsjóndin skal lætta um móttøku og nýtslu av Kodi fyri nýggjar brúkarar.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Confluence Extended est une combinaison de concepts provenant de plusieurs habillages populaires. Il tente d'inclure et d'intégrer leurs bonnes idées en un habillage qui devrait être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Confluence Extended est l'habillage d'origine depuis Kodi 14.0. Reprenant les concepts issus de plusieurs habillages populaires, il est une tentative d'inclusion et d'intégration des meilleures idées afin de créer un habillage d'interface qui soit facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les personnes découvrant Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Confluence Extended é a pel predeterminada para Kodi 14.0 e posteriores. É unha combinación de conceptos de algunhas peles populares, e tenta abranguer e integrar  as súas mellores ideas nunha pel que sexa fácil de entender e utilizar para as usuarias que utilizan por primeira vez Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">המעטפת Confluence Extended היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של Kodi. המעטפת הינה תוצר של אימוץ מאפיינים ממעטפות פופולריות רבות תוך רצון לשלב מאפיינים אלה למעטפת פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית ע"י משתמשי Kodi חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Confluence Extended je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi 14.0 naviše. To je mješavina koncepta iz mnogih drugih popularnih presvlaka, pokušaj da se objedine njihove dobre osobine u presvlaku i da budu lagane za upotrebu i razumljive novim Kodi korisnicima.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">A Confluence Extended az alapértelmezett felszín a Kodihoz a 14.0-es verziótól kezdődően. Merít sok sok népszerű felszín elképzeléséből, megpróbálva vegyíteni a jó ötleteket úgy, hogy az könnyen kezelhető legyen a Kodival először találkozóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Confluence Extended merupakan skin bawaan untuk Kodi 14.0 dan selanjutnya. Merupakan kombinasi konsep dari beberapa skin populer, dan berusaha untuk merangkul dan menyatukan ide bagus mereka ke sebuah skin yang mudah dipakai dan dipahami oleh pengguna Kodi pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Confluence Extended er sjálfgefið útlit Kodi 14.0 og nýrra. Það er samsetning hugmynda frá mörgum vinsælum útlitum og er tilraun til að fanga og innlima þær góðu hugmyndir í útlit sem sé einfalt fyrir fyrir nýja Kodi notendur að skilja og nota</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Confluence Extended è la skin predefinita di Kodi dalla versione 14.0 in poi. È una combinazione di elementi provenienti da altre skin popolari e cerca di integrare e coinvolgere tutte le loro grandi idee in una skin facile da usare e comprendere per l'utente inesperto di Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">Confluence Extended は Kodi 9.11 およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。さまざまな人気のスキンのコンセプトを組み合わせ、ユーザが初めて Kodi に触れる際に便利に使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Confluence Extended 는 Kodi 14.0 이상을 위한 기본 스킨입니다. 많은 인기 스킨의 컨셉과 좋은 아이디어를 모아서 하나의 스킨으로 만들었으며 초보자도 사용하기 쉽습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Confluence Extended yra numatytoji teminė išvaizda pradedant Kodi 14.0 versija. Tai daugelio populiarių teminų išvaizdų derinys. Bandymas priimti ir integruoti vartotojų idėjas į teminę išvaizdą katra turėtų būti lengvai suprantama  pirmą kartą naudojantiems Kodi</description>
		<description lang="lv_LV">Confluence Extended ir Kodi 9.11 un jaunāku versiju noklusētais apvalks. Tajā apvienota daudzu populāru apvalku koncepcija un centieni pieņemt un integrēt labākās idejas, lai jaunajiem Kodi ietotājiem to būtu viegli izprast un lietot.</description>
		<description lang="mk_MK">Confluence Extended е основниот изглед на Kodi 14.0 и нагоре. Тој е комбинација на концепти од повеќе популарни изгледи, и настојува да ги обедини и истакне нивните добри идеи во еден изглед разбирлив за почетници.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Penyatuan ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 9.11 dan ke atas. Ia merupakan gabungan konsep dari pelbagai kulit terkenal, dan berusaha untuk merangkumkan dan menyepadukan idea baik kulit-kulit tersebut menjadi satu kulit yang mudah difahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna baru Kodi .</description>
		<description lang="mt_MT">Confluence Extended hija d-dehra normali ta' Kodi 14.0 il-fuq.  Hija taħlita ta' kunċetti minn ħafna dehriet popolari, u tipporva tgħaqqad u tintegra l-aqwa ideat tagħhom f'dehra li għandha tkun faċli biex jifmuha u jużawha dawk l-utenti li qed jużaw Kodi għall-ewwel darba.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Confluence Extended er standardskallet for Kodi 14.0 og oppover. Det er en kombinasjon av konseptene fra mange populære skall, og prøver å omfavne og integrere de gode idéene i et skall som bør være lett å forstå og benytte seg av for nye Kodi-brukere.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Confluence Extended is de standaard skin voor Kodi 14.0 en hoger. Het combineert de concepten van andere populaire skins, waarbij het tracht hun goede ideeën te integreren in een skin die gemakkelijk in gebruik is.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Confluence Extended jest kombinacją koncepcji  wielu popularnych skór i próbą zawarcia tego, co w nich najlepsze w skórze, która będzie łatwa do opanowania dla początkującego użytkownika.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Confluence Extended é a skin padrão do Kodi 9.11 e acima. É uma combinação de conceitos das mais populares skins, visando abraçar e integrar as boas ideias em uma skin  que seja fácil de entender e usar, destinada  aos usuários iniciantes do Kodi. </description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O tema "Confluence Extended" é o tema padrão do Kodi 14.0 e superior. É uma combinação de conceitos a partir de muitos temas populares e tenta integrar as boas ideias dos mesmos, num tema que deverá ser fácil de entender e utilizar pelos novos utilizadores do Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Confluence Extended este costumul implicit pentru Kodi 14.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Este o combinație de concepte împrumutate de la mai multe costume populare, care încearcă să îmbrățișeze și să integreze ideile lor bune într-un costum care să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit de către utilizatorii Kodi începători.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Confluence Extended — это модернизированная обложка KODI. Она представляет собой сочетание концепций, взятых из многих популярных обложек, в попытке интегрировать их удачные идеи в обложке, которая была простой для использования и понимания новыми пользователями KODI.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Confluence Extended je predvolený pre Kodi 14.0 a vyššie. Je kombináciou konceptov z mnoho populárnych skinov a pokusom integrovať ich dobré nápady do skinu, ktorý by bol ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sl_SI">Confluence Extended je privzeta preobleka za Kodi 14.0 in novejše. Je kombinacija konceptov mnogih priljubljenih preoblek in poskuša zaobjeti in integrirati njihove dobre ideje v preobleko, ki bi bila preprosta za uporabo in razumevanje tudi novim uporabnikom.</description>
		<description lang="sq_AL">Confluence Extended është maska kryesore për Kodi 14.0 dhe verzionet më të lartë. Është nje kombinim nga shumë maska e popullarizuar dhe përpjeket për të përqafuar dhe integruar idetë më të mira në një maskë që të jetë sa më lehtë në përdorim dhe kuptim për përdoruasit duke e përdorur Kodi për herë të parë.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Confluence Extended је мешавина концепата из многих других популарних маски, и покушај да се обједине њихове добре идеје у маску која би трабала да буде лака за разумевање и употребу новим корисницима Kodi-а.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Confluence Extended je mešavina koncepata iz mnogih drugih popularnih maski, i pokušaj da se objedine njihove dobre ideje u masku koja bi trabala da bude laka za razumevanje i upotrebu novim korisnicima Kodi-a.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Confluence Extended är standardskal för Kodi 14.0 och senare. Det kombinerar koncept från många populära skal och försöker återanvända och integrera goda idéer för att skapa ett skal som är enkelt att förstå och använda för nya Kode-användare.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Confluence Extended to je wychodnŏ skōra dlŏ Kodi 14.0 i nowszych. To je miszōng kōnceptōw ze mocki popularnych skōr i prōbuje te nŏjlepsze wkludzić do skōry, kerŏ winnŏ być prostŏ we użyciu i spokopiyniu dlŏ nowych używŏczōw Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="tg_TJ">Пӯсти ҳамҷараёнӣ ҳамчун пӯсти пешфарз барои Kodi 14.0 ё версияи навтар истифода мешавад. Ин пӯст аз унсурҳои пӯстҳои машҳури дигар сохта шудааст ва ва ҳамаи фикрҳои беҳтарин дар як пӯст ҷамъ мекунад, то ки корбарони навомад тавонанд Kodi-ро ба осонӣ фаҳманд ва истифода баранд.</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Confluence Extended เป็นสกินเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi 14.0 หรือสูงกว่า มันเป็นส่วนผสมของแนวคิดจากสกินที่ได้รับความนิยมและพยายามที่จะยอมรับและบูรณาการส่วนที่ดีของมันเข้าไปในสกิน ซึ่งน่าจะง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodiใหม่ ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งานได้ดี</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Confluence Extended Kodi 14.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. Birçok popüler dış görünümün kavramlarını bir araya getirip ilk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Confluence Extended — це модернізована обкладинка Kodi. Концепції багатьох популярних обкладинок поєднано у спробі використати та інтегрувати їхні вдалі ідеї в обкладинці, що стала б зрозумілою та простою в застосуванні для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Confluence Extended là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 14.0 and các phiên bản trở về trước. Đây là sự kết hợp các khái niệm đến từ các giao diện khác nhau nhằm hướng người dùng đến sự đơn giản và dễ sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Confluence Extended 集合了许多流行皮肤的创意，力求把这些优点融合到一个皮肤中，使得首次使用 Kodi 的用户能更容易上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Confluence Extended 是從 Kodi 9.11 開始預設的佈景主題。它結合了許多受歡迎的佈景主題的概念，且試圖包含並整合它們的優點，使第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU General Public License version 2</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=125</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/skin.confluence-extended.git</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-09.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<news>Updated language files</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon
	id="skin.confluence-extended-s"
	version="3.1.6.153"
	name="Confluence Extended Shortcuts"
	provider-name="Jezz_X, Team Kodi, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
		<import addon="script.image.resource.select" version="1.1.0"/>
		<import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="1.0.10"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.service" version="1.0.10"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.skinbackup" version="1.0.10"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.widgets" version="1.0.10"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.backgrounds" version="1.0.10"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.colorpicker" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension
		point="xbmc.gui.skin"
		defaultthemename="Textures.xbt"
		debugging="false"
		effectslowdown="1.0">
		<res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Confluence Extended Shortcuts oortreksel deur Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi se standaard tema)</summary>
		<summary lang="ar_SA">جلد "كونفليونس" من صنع Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (الجلد المبدأى لبرنامج إكس بى إم سى)</summary>
		<summary lang="be_BY">Confluence Extended Shortcuts skin by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Confluence Extended Shortcuts облик от Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (стандартния облик за Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Confluence Extended Shortcuts, per Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Pell per defecte del Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Confluence Extended Shortcuts od Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cy_GB">Croen Confluence Extended Shortcuts gan Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Croen rhagosodedig Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Confluence Extended Shortcuts-tema af Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodis standardtema)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Confluence Extended Shortcuts Skin von Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Standard-Skin von Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Confluence Extended Shortcuts από τον Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="en_AU">Confluence Extended Shortcuts skin by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Confluence Extended Shortcuts skin by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Confluence Extended Shortcuts skin by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Confluence Extended Shortcuts skin by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Confluence Extended Shortcuts skin por Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Confluence Extended Shortcuts skin por Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (skin por defecto)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Skin confluende por Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Confluence Extended Shortcuts rüü autorilt Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi vaikerüü)</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Confluence Extended Shortcuts azala Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood egina.</summary>
		<summary lang="fa_IR">پوسته Confluence Extended Shortcuts تهیه شده بوسیله Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (پوسته پیش فرض Kodi) </summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Confluence Extended Shortcuts-ulkoasu. Tekijä Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="fo_FO">Confluence Extended Shortcuts útsjónd av Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's vanliga útsjónd)</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Confluence Extended Shortcuts par Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Thème Confluence Extended Shortcuts par Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Habillage d'origine de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Confluence Extended Shortcuts por Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">המעטפת Confluence Extended Shortcuts של Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (ברירת המחדל של Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Confluence Extended Shortcuts presvlaka autora Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (uobičajena Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Confluence Extended Shortcuts felszín. Készítő: Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="hy_AM">''Confluence Extended Shortcuts'' - տեսք՝ Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. կողմից (Kodi - հիմնական տեսք)</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Skin Confluence Extended Shortcuts oleh Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Skin bawaan Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Confluence Extended Shortcuts eftir Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Sjálfgefið útlit Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Confluence Extended Shortcuts da Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Confluence Extended Shortcuts スキン by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">Confluence Extended Shortcuts 스킨 Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood 만듦 (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Confluence Extended Shortcuts teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi numatytoji teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Confluence Extended Shortcuts apvalks no Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi noklusētais apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Confluence Extended Shortcuts skin by Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's default skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Penyatuan, kulit daripada Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="mt_MT">Dehra Confluence Extended Shortcuts magħmula minn Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Id-dehra normali ta' Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Confluence Extended Shortcuts-skall av Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodis standardskall)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Confluence Extended Shortcuts skin door Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi's standaard skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Confluence Extended Shortcuts autorstwa Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Confluence Extended Shortcuts por Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Tema Confluence Extended Shortcuts por Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood (tema padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Costum Confluence Extended Shortcuts de Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (costum implicit pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Confluence Extended Shortcuts. Авторы: Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Confluence Extended Shortcuts skin od Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (predvolený skin Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sl_SI">Preobleka Confluence Extended Shortcuts avtorja Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Privzeta preobleka za Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sq_AL">Maska Confluence Extended Shortcuts nga Jazz_X (maska kryesore së Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Confluence Extended Shortcuts маска аутора Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Confluence Extended Shortcuts maska autora Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Confluence Extended Shortcuts, ett skal av Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Kodi:s standardskal)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Confluence Extended Shortcuts zrychtowanŏ ôd Jeez_X. (wychodnŏ skōra we Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tg_TJ">Пӯсти ҳамҷараёнӣ аз ҷониби Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Пӯсти пешфарзи Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">ชุดตกแต่ง Confluence Extended Shortcuts โดย  Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood (สกินเริ่มต้นของ Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Confluence Extended Shortcuts dış görünümü. Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood (Kodi'nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Confluence Extended Shortcuts. Автори: Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood.</summary>
		<summary lang="vi_VN">Giao diện Confluence Extended Shortcuts bởi Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood. (Giao diện mặc định của Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood 开发的 Confluence Extended Shortcuts 皮肤。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">Jezz_X, Team XBMC, YLLOW_DRAGON, plood 製作的佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Confluence Extended Shortcuts is die standaard oortreksel vir Kodi 14.0 en op. Dit is 'n kombinasie van konsepte van 'n klomp gewilde oortreksels, en 'n poging om hulle goeie idees te omvat en te integreer in 'n oortreksel wat maklik behoort te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="ar_SA">"كونفليونس" هو الجلد المبدأى لبرنامج إكس بى إم سى اﻹصدار 9.11 وما فوق. هو خلط بين اشهر اﻷجلده الاخرى معاً ومحاوله لتبنى ودمج افكارهم للخروج بِنِتَاج يُفترض به ان يكون سهل اﻹستيعاب بمجرد النظر لمستخدمى إكس بى إم سى المبتدئين.</description>
		<description lang="be_BY">Confluence Extended Shortcuts is the default skin for Kodi 14.0 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Confluence Extended Shortcuts е стандартният облик на Kodi 14.0 и по-новите версии. Представлява смесица от концепциите на много от популярните облици. Целта е да се интегрират тези добри идеи в подходящ и удобен вид за хора, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Confluence Extended Shortcuts és la pell per defecte del Kodi 14.0 i superiors. És una combinació de conceptes de moltes pells populars que intenta adoptar i integrar les seves bones idees en una aparença que sigui senzilla d'entendre i utilitzar per els nous usuaris de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Confluence Extended Shortcuts je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 14.0 a novější. Jedná se o kombinaci konceptů z mnoha jiných populárních vzhledů, která se pokouší uchopit a integrovat jejich dobré nápady do vzhledu, který by měl být pro nového uživatele Kodi jednoduchý na pochopení a používání.</description>
		<description lang="cy_GB">Confluence Extended Shortcuts yw croen rhagosodedig Kodi 14.0 ac uwch. Mae'n gyfuniad o gysyniadau o nifer o grwyn poblogaidd ac mae'n ymdrechu i gyfuno eu syniadau da hwy i groen ddylai fod yn hawdd i ddefnyddiwr cyntaf Kodi ei deall a'i ddefnyddio.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Confluence Extended Shortcuts er standardskin'et til Kodi 14.0 og senere versioner. Det er en kombination af koncepter fra mange populære skins, og det forsøger at omfavne og integrere de gode ideer i et skin, der er let for førstegangsbrugere af Kodi at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Confluence Extended Shortcuts ist der Standardskin ab Kodi 14.0. Er ist eine Kombination mehrerer unterschiedlicher Skin-Konzepte und versucht dabei, die besten Ideen zu kombinieren, um einen einfachen Einstieg für neue Kodi-Nutzer zu ermöglichen.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Confluence Extended Shortcuts είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 14.0 και άνω. Είναι ένας συνδυασμός από πολλές δημοφιλής αμφιέσεις, και επιχειρεί να παρέχει τις καλύτερες ιδέες τους σε μία αμφίεση, το οποίο είναι εύκολο για τους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi να κατανοήσουν και να χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_AU">Confluence Extended Shortcuts is the modernized skin for KODI. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Confluence Extended Shortcuts is the modernized skin for KODI. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Confluence Extended Shortcuts is the modernized skin for KODI. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Confluence Extended Shortcuts is the modernized skin for KODI. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Confluence Extended Shortcuts es el skin por defecto de Kodi 14.0 y posteriores. Es una combinación de conceptos de muchos skins populares, e intenta abarcar e integrar lo mejor de ellos en un skin que sea sencillo de entender y utilizar para los nuevos usuarios de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Confluence Extended Shortcuts es la skin por defecto de Kodi 14.0 y posteriores. Es una combinación de conceptos de muchas skins populares, e intenta abarcar e integrar lo mejor de ellas en una skin que sea sencilla de entender y utilizar para los nuevos usuarios de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Confluence Extended Shortcuts es el skin por defecto para Kodi 14.0 en adelante. Es una combinación de conceptos de varias skins populares, e intenta adoptar e integrar sus buenas ideas en un skin que debería ser fá de entender y usar para quienes usen Kodi por primera vez.</description>
		<description lang="et_EE">Confluence Extended Shortcuts on Kodi vaikerüü alates versioonist 14.0. Confluence Extended Shortcuts on paljude populaarsete rüüde kombinatsioon, üritades omavahel siduda nende parimaid lahendusi, et saavutada esmakasutajale selget ja kergelt kasutatavat tulemust.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Confluence Extended Shortcuts hainbat azal ospetsutatik hartutako kontzeptuen konbinaketa da. Horietatik ideia onak hartu eta integratzen saiatzen da, Kodi lehen aldiz erabiltzen dutenentzat ulertzeko eta erabiltzeko erraza izango den azal batean.</description>
		<description lang="fa_IR">Confluence Extended Shortcuts پوسته پیش فرض Kodi در ویرایش 14 و بالاتر است. این پوسته ترکیبی از چند پوسته محبوب دیگر است و تلاش دارد بهترین ایده ها را با هم ترکیب کند، تا شروعی ساده و آسان را برای کاربران جدید Kodi امکان پذیر سازد.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Confluence Extended Shortcuts on yhdistelmä useiden suosittujen ulkoasujen konsepteista, ja yritys omaksua ja integroida heidän hyvät ideat ulkoasuun, jonka pitäisi olla helppokäyttöinen ja -tajuinen kaikille Kodin käyttäjille.</description>
		<description lang="fo_FO">Confluence Extended Shortcuts er vanliga útsjóndin, sum er brúkt í Kodi síðan útg. 14.0. Hetta er ein samansjóðan av fleiri hugtøkum. Ætlanin er at útsjóndin skal lætta um móttøku og nýtslu av Kodi fyri nýggjar brúkarar.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Confluence Extended Shortcuts est une combinaison de concepts provenant de plusieurs habillages populaires. Il tente d'inclure et d'intégrer leurs bonnes idées en un habillage qui devrait être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Confluence Extended Shortcuts est l'habillage d'origine depuis Kodi 14.0. Reprenant les concepts issus de plusieurs habillages populaires, il est une tentative d'inclusion et d'intégration des meilleures idées afin de créer un habillage d'interface qui soit facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les personnes découvrant Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Confluence Extended Shortcuts é a pel predeterminada para Kodi 14.0 e posteriores. É unha combinación de conceptos de algunhas peles populares, e tenta abranguer e integrar  as súas mellores ideas nunha pel que sexa fácil de entender e utilizar para as usuarias que utilizan por primeira vez Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">המעטפת Confluence Extended Shortcuts היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של Kodi. המעטפת הינה תוצר של אימוץ מאפיינים ממעטפות פופולריות רבות תוך רצון לשלב מאפיינים אלה למעטפת פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית ע"י משתמשי Kodi חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Confluence Extended Shortcuts je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi 14.0 naviše. To je mješavina koncepta iz mnogih drugih popularnih presvlaka, pokušaj da se objedine njihove dobre osobine u presvlaku i da budu lagane za upotrebu i razumljive novim Kodi korisnicima.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">A Confluence Extended Shortcuts az alapértelmezett felszín a Kodihoz a 14.0-es verziótól kezdődően. Merít sok sok népszerű felszín elképzeléséből, megpróbálva vegyíteni a jó ötleteket úgy, hogy az könnyen kezelhető legyen a Kodival először találkozóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Confluence Extended Shortcuts merupakan skin bawaan untuk Kodi 14.0 dan selanjutnya. Merupakan kombinasi konsep dari beberapa skin populer, dan berusaha untuk merangkul dan menyatukan ide bagus mereka ke sebuah skin yang mudah dipakai dan dipahami oleh pengguna Kodi pertama kali.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Confluence Extended Shortcuts er sjálfgefið útlit Kodi 14.0 og nýrra. Það er samsetning hugmynda frá mörgum vinsælum útlitum og er tilraun til að fanga og innlima þær góðu hugmyndir í útlit sem sé einfalt fyrir fyrir nýja Kodi notendur að skilja og nota</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Confluence Extended Shortcuts è la skin predefinita di Kodi dalla versione 14.0 in poi. È una combinazione di elementi provenienti da altre skin popolari e cerca di integrare e coinvolgere tutte le loro grandi idee in una skin facile da usare e comprendere per l'utente inesperto di Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">Confluence Extended Shortcuts は Kodi 9.11 およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。さまざまな人気のスキンのコンセプトを組み合わせ、ユーザが初めて Kodi に触れる際に便利に使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Confluence Extended Shortcuts 는 Kodi 14.0 이상을 위한 기본 스킨입니다. 많은 인기 스킨의 컨셉과 좋은 아이디어를 모아서 하나의 스킨으로 만들었으며 초보자도 사용하기 쉽습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Confluence Extended Shortcuts yra numatytoji teminė išvaizda pradedant Kodi 14.0 versija. Tai daugelio populiarių teminų išvaizdų derinys. Bandymas priimti ir integruoti vartotojų idėjas į teminę išvaizdą katra turėtų būti lengvai suprantama  pirmą kartą naudojantiems Kodi</description>
		<description lang="lv_LV">Confluence Extended Shortcuts ir Kodi 9.11 un jaunāku versiju noklusētais apvalks. Tajā apvienota daudzu populāru apvalku koncepcija un centieni pieņemt un integrēt labākās idejas, lai jaunajiem Kodi ietotājiem to būtu viegli izprast un lietot.</description>
		<description lang="mk_MK">Confluence Extended Shortcuts е основниот изглед на Kodi 14.0 и нагоре. Тој е комбинација на концепти од повеќе популарни изгледи, и настојува да ги обедини и истакне нивните добри идеи во еден изглед разбирлив за почетници.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Penyatuan ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 9.11 dan ke atas. Ia merupakan gabungan konsep dari pelbagai kulit terkenal, dan berusaha untuk merangkumkan dan menyepadukan idea baik kulit-kulit tersebut menjadi satu kulit yang mudah difahami dan digunakan oleh pengguna baru Kodi .</description>
		<description lang="mt_MT">Confluence Extended Shortcuts hija d-dehra normali ta' Kodi 14.0 il-fuq.  Hija taħlita ta' kunċetti minn ħafna dehriet popolari, u tipporva tgħaqqad u tintegra l-aqwa ideat tagħhom f'dehra li għandha tkun faċli biex jifmuha u jużawha dawk l-utenti li qed jużaw Kodi għall-ewwel darba.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Confluence Extended Shortcuts er standardskallet for Kodi 14.0 og oppover. Det er en kombinasjon av konseptene fra mange populære skall, og prøver å omfavne og integrere de gode idéene i et skall som bør være lett å forstå og benytte seg av for nye Kodi-brukere.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Confluence Extended Shortcuts is de standaard skin voor Kodi 14.0 en hoger. Het combineert de concepten van andere populaire skins, waarbij het tracht hun goede ideeën te integreren in een skin die gemakkelijk in gebruik is.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Confluence Extended Shortcuts jest kombinacją koncepcji  wielu popularnych skór i próbą zawarcia tego, co w nich najlepsze w skórze, która będzie łatwa do opanowania dla początkującego użytkownika.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Confluence Extended Shortcuts é a skin padrão do Kodi 9.11 e acima. É uma combinação de conceitos das mais populares skins, visando abraçar e integrar as boas ideias em uma skin  que seja fácil de entender e usar, destinada  aos usuários iniciantes do Kodi. </description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O tema "Confluence Extended Shortcuts" é o tema padrão do Kodi 14.0 e superior. É uma combinação de conceitos a partir de muitos temas populares e tenta integrar as boas ideias dos mesmos, num tema que deverá ser fácil de entender e utilizar pelos novos utilizadores do Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Confluence Extended Shortcuts este costumul implicit pentru Kodi 14.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Este o combinație de concepte împrumutate de la mai multe costume populare, care încearcă să îmbrățișeze și să integreze ideile lor bune într-un costum care să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit de către utilizatorii Kodi începători.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Confluence Extended Shortcuts — это модернизированная обложка KODI. Она представляет собой сочетание концепций, взятых из многих популярных обложек, в попытке интегрировать их удачные идеи в обложке, которая была простой для использования и понимания новыми пользователями KODI.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Confluence Extended Shortcuts je predvolený pre Kodi 14.0 a vyššie. Je kombináciou konceptov z mnoho populárnych skinov a pokusom integrovať ich dobré nápady do skinu, ktorý by bol ľahko zrozumiteľný a použiteľný pre nových používateľov Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sl_SI">Confluence Extended Shortcuts je privzeta preobleka za Kodi 14.0 in novejše. Je kombinacija konceptov mnogih priljubljenih preoblek in poskuša zaobjeti in integrirati njihove dobre ideje v preobleko, ki bi bila preprosta za uporabo in razumevanje tudi novim uporabnikom.</description>
		<description lang="sq_AL">Confluence Extended Shortcuts është maska kryesore për Kodi 14.0 dhe verzionet më të lartë. Është nje kombinim nga shumë maska e popullarizuar dhe përpjeket për të përqafuar dhe integruar idetë më të mira në një maskë që të jetë sa më lehtë në përdorim dhe kuptim për përdoruasit duke e përdorur Kodi për herë të parë.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Confluence Extended Shortcuts је мешавина концепата из многих других популарних маски, и покушај да се обједине њихове добре идеје у маску која би трабала да буде лака за разумевање и употребу новим корисницима Kodi-а.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Confluence Extended Shortcuts je mešavina koncepata iz mnogih drugih popularnih maski, i pokušaj da se objedine njihove dobre ideje u masku koja bi trabala da bude laka za razumevanje i upotrebu novim korisnicima Kodi-a.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Confluence Extended Shortcuts är standardskal för Kodi 14.0 och senare. Det kombinerar koncept från många populära skal och försöker återanvända och integrera goda idéer för att skapa ett skal som är enkelt att förstå och använda för nya Kode-användare.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Confluence Extended Shortcuts to je wychodnŏ skōra dlŏ Kodi 14.0 i nowszych. To je miszōng kōnceptōw ze mocki popularnych skōr i prōbuje te nŏjlepsze wkludzić do skōry, kerŏ winnŏ być prostŏ we użyciu i spokopiyniu dlŏ nowych używŏczōw Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="tg_TJ">Пӯсти ҳамҷараёнӣ ҳамчун пӯсти пешфарз барои Kodi 14.0 ё версияи навтар истифода мешавад. Ин пӯст аз унсурҳои пӯстҳои машҳури дигар сохта шудааст ва ва ҳамаи фикрҳои беҳтарин дар як пӯст ҷамъ мекунад, то ки корбарони навомад тавонанд Kodi-ро ба осонӣ фаҳманд ва истифода баранд.</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Confluence Extended Shortcuts เป็นสกินเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi 14.0 หรือสูงกว่า มันเป็นส่วนผสมของแนวคิดจากสกินที่ได้รับความนิยมและพยายามที่จะยอมรับและบูรณาการส่วนที่ดีของมันเข้าไปในสกิน ซึ่งน่าจะง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodiใหม่ ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งานได้ดี</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Confluence Extended Shortcuts Kodi 14.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. Birçok popüler dış görünümün kavramlarını bir araya getirip ilk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Confluence Extended Shortcuts — це модернізована обкладинка Kodi. Концепції багатьох популярних обкладинок поєднано у спробі використати та інтегрувати їхні вдалі ідеї в обкладинці, що стала б зрозумілою та простою в застосуванні для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="vi_VN">Confluence Extended Shortcuts là giao diện mặc định cho Kodi 14.0 and các phiên bản trở về trước. Đây là sự kết hợp các khái niệm đến từ các giao diện khác nhau nhằm hướng người dùng đến sự đơn giản và dễ sử dụng.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Confluence Extended Shortcuts 集合了许多流行皮肤的创意，力求把这些优点融合到一个皮肤中，使得首次使用 Kodi 的用户能更容易上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Confluence Extended Shortcuts 是從 Kodi 9.11 開始預設的佈景主題。它結合了許多受歡迎的佈景主題的概念，且試圖包含並整合它們的優點，使第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU General Public License version 2</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=125</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/skin.confluence-extended.git</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-09.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<news>Updated language files</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon
	id="skin.estuary2-extended"
	version="1.9.16.097"
	name="Estuary v2 Extended"
	provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
		<import addon="script.pvr.favourites" version="2.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.image.resource.select" version="1.1.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension
		point="xbmc.gui.skin"
		debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary v2 Extended oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary v2 Extended облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary v2 Extended per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary v2 Extended od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary v2 Extended skin. Lavet af phil65. (Kodi's standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary v2 Extended Skin von phil65 und Piers. (Kodi Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary v2 Extended από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary v2 Extended skin by phil65, Piers, YLLOW_DRAGON.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary v2 Extended skin by phil65, Piers, YLLOW_DRAGON.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary v2 Extended skin by phil65, Piers, YLLOW_DRAGON.</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary v2 Extended por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary v2 Extended, creado por phil65 and Piers (skin por defecto de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Estuary v2 Extended skin por phil65 y Piers. (El skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary v2 Extended on phil65:n luoma Kodin oletusulkoasu.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary v2 Extended par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary v2 Extended, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d'origine de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary v2 Extended por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary v2 Extended של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary v2 Extended presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (uobičajena Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary v2 Extended felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary v2 Extended da phil65 e Piers. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuary v2 Extended スキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65와 Piers가 만든 Estuary v2 Extended 스킨 (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary v2 Extended teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary v2 Extended apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary v2 Extended oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Estuary v2 Extended-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary v2 Extended skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi's standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Estuary v2 Extended autorstwa phil65 i Piers. (Domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary v2 Extended por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary v2 Extended de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary v2 Extended de phil65 și Piers. (Tema implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary v2 Extended. Авторы: phil65, Piers, YLLOW_DRAGON.</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary v2 Extended, vytvorili phil65 a Piers. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary v2 Extended аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary v2 Extended autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary v2 Extended-skin av phil65 och Piers. (Kodi's standard-skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary v2 Extended ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodnŏ skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary v2 Extended โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary v2 Extended dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi'nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary v2 Extended від phil65, Piers, YLLOW_DRAGON.</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 和 Piers 开发的 Estuary v2 Extended 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary v2 Extended佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary v2 Extended is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary v2 Extended е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary v2 Extended és l'aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d'entendre i d'utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary v2 Extended je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary v2 Extended er standard  brugerfladen er Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen  af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmer at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary v2 Extended ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary v2 Extended είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary v2 Extended  - is the modernized skin for Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary v2 Extended  - is the modernized skin for Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary v2 Extended  - is the modernized skin for Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary v2 Extended es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary v2 Extended es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary v2 Extended es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Intenta ser fácil para los usuarios de Kodi de primera vez para entender y usar.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary v2 Extended on oletusulkoasu Kodin versiosta 17.0 lähtien. Se pyrkii olemaan helppo ymmärtää ja käyttää Kodin ensikäyttäjille. </description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary v2 Extended est l'habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s'efforce d'être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary v2 Extended est l'habillage d'origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary v2 Extended é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Estuary v2 Extended הינה מעטפת ברירת המחדל של Kodi מגרסאת 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית ע"י משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary v2 Extended je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary v2 Extended az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban.  Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary v2 Extended è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e usare per i nuovi utenti di Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">Estuary v2 Extended は Kodi 17.0 およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザが初めて Kodi に触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary v2 Extended는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary v2 Extended yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary v2 Extended ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary v2 Extended er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary v2 Extended is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Estuary v2 Extended jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary v2 Extended é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary v2 Extended é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary v2 Extended este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary v2 Extended - это модернизированная обложка KODI.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary v2 Extended je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Pokúša sa byť pre prvotných používateľov Kodi jednoduchým na pochopenie a používanie.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary v2 Extended је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary v2 Extended je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary v2 Extended är standard-skin för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det försöker att vara lättförståeligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi att förstå och använda.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary v2 Extended je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary v2 Extended คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary v2 Extended Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary v2 Extended є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary v2 Extended 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary v2 Extended是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Estuary v2 Extended is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary v2 Extended е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary v2 Extended és l'aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s'elimina pot causar problemes.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary v2 Extended je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary v2 Extended er standard  brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary v2 Extended ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary v2 Extended είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary v2 Extended  - is the modernized skin for Kodi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary v2 Extended  - is the modernized skin for Kodi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary v2 Extended  - is the modernized skin for Kodi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary v2 Extended es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary v2 Extended es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Desinstalarlo puede causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary v2 Extended es el skin por defecto para Kodi, su eliminación puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary v2 Extended on Kodin oletusulkoasu, sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary v2 Extended est l'habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary v2 Extended est l'habillage d'origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary v2 Extended é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary v2 Extended הינה מעטפת ברירת המחדל של Kodi, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary v2 Extended je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi, njegovim uklanjanjem može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary v2 Extended az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary v2 Extended è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">Estuary v2 Extended は Kodi のデフォルトスキンですので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary v2 Extended는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary v2 Extended yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary v2 Extended ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary v2 Extended er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary v2 Extended is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary v2 Extended kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Estuary v2 Extended jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary v2 Extended é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary v2 Extended é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary v2 Extended este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary v2 Extended - это модернизированная обложка KODI</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary v2 Extended je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary v2 Extended је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary v2 Extended je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary v2 Extended är standard skalet för Kodi, ta bort den kan orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary v2 Extended je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary v2 Extended เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary v2 Extended Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary v2 Extended — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary v2 Extended 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary v2 Extended 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/skin.estuary2-extended.git</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-09.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-10.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-11.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-12.png</screenshot>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon
	id="skin.estuary2-extended-s"
	version="1.9.16.126"
	name="Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts"
	provider-name="phil65, Ichabod Fletchman, YLLOW_DRAGON">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
		<import addon="script.pvr.favourites" version="2.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.image.resource.select" version="1.1.0"/>
		<import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="1.0.10"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.service" version="1.0.10"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.skinbackup" version="1.0.10"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.widgets" version="1.0.10"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.backgrounds" version="1.0.10"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.colorpicker" version="1.0.0"/>
		<import addon="resource.images.skinicons.estuary" version="1.0.0"/>
		<import addon="resource.images.busyspinners.estuary" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension
		point="xbmc.gui.skin"
		debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts oortreksel deur phil65. (Kodi se bestek oortreksel)</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts облик от phil65 и Piers. (стандартния облик на Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts per phil65 i Piers. (aparença predeterminada de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts od autora phil65. (Výchozí vzhled Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts skin. Lavet af phil65. (Kodi's standard brugerflade)</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts Skin von phil65 und Piers. (Kodi Standardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts από τον phil65 και τον Pier. (προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος του Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts skin by phil65, Piers, YLLOW_DRAGON.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts skin by phil65, Piers, YLLOW_DRAGON.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts skin by phil65, Piers, YLLOW_DRAGON.</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts por phil65 (skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts, creado por phil65 and Piers (skin por defecto de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts skin por phil65 y Piers. (El skin por defecto de Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts on phil65:n luoma Kodin oletusulkoasu.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts par phil65 et Piers (habillage par défaut de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts, un habillage par phil65 et Piers (habillage d'origine de Kodi).</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts por phil65 and Piers. (Pel predefinida do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts של phil65 (ברירת המחדל של Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts presvlaka autora phil65 i Piersa. (uobičajena Kodi presvlaka)</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts felszín. Készítette phil65 és Piers. (Kodi alapértelmezett felszín)</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts da phil65 e Piers. (Skin predefinita di Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts スキン by phil65 and Piers (Kodi デフォルトスキン)</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">phil65와 Piers가 만든 Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts 스킨 (Kodi 기본 스킨)</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė phil65 ir Piers. (Numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda)</summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts apvalks no phil65. (Kodi noklusējuma apvalks)</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts oleh phil65 dan rakan-rakan. (Kulit lalai Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts-drakt av phil65 og Piers. (Kodis forvalgte drakt)</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts skin door phil65 en Piers. (Kodi's standaardskin)</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts autorstwa phil65 i Piers. (Domyślna skóra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts por phil65 e Piers. (Skin padrão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts de phil65 e Piers. (Visual por omissão do Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts de phil65 și Piers. (Tema implicită pentru Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts. Авторы: phil65, Piers, YLLOW_DRAGON.</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts, vytvorili phil65 a Piers. (predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts аутора phil65 и Piers. (Подразумевана Коди маска)</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts autora phil65 i Piers. (Podrazumevana Kodi maska)</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts-skin av phil65 och Piers. (Kodi's standard-skin)</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts ôd phil65 i Piers. (Wychodnŏ skōra Kodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts โดย phil65 และ Piers (หน้าตาเริ่มต้นของKodi)</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts dış görünümü. phil65 (Kodi'nin varsayılan dış görünümü)</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts від phil65, Piers, YLLOW_DRAGON.</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">phil65 和 Piers 开发的 Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts 皮肤（Kodi 的默认皮肤）</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">phil65與Piers 製作的Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts佈景主題（Kodi的預設佈景主題）</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts és l'aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d'entendre i d'utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts er standard  brugerfladen er Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen  af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmer at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts  - is the modernized skin for Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts  - is the modernized skin for Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts  - is the modernized skin for Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Intenta ser fácil para los usuarios de Kodi de primera vez para entender y usar.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts on oletusulkoasu Kodin versiosta 17.0 lähtien. Se pyrkii olemaan helppo ymmärtää ja käyttää Kodin ensikäyttäjille. </description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts est l'habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s'efforce d'être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts est l'habillage d'origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts הינה מעטפת ברירת המחדל של Kodi מגרסאת 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית ע"י משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban.  Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e usare per i nuovi utenti di Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts は Kodi 17.0 およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザが初めて Kodi に触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts - это модернизированная обложка KODI.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Pokúša sa byť pre prvotných používateľov Kodi jednoduchým na pochopenie a používanie.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts är standard-skin för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det försöker att vara lättförståeligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi att förstå och använda.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts és l'aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s'elimina pot causar problemes.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts er standard  brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts  - is the modernized skin for Kodi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts  - is the modernized skin for Kodi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts  - is the modernized skin for Kodi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Desinstalarlo puede causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts es el skin por defecto para Kodi, su eliminación puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts on Kodin oletusulkoasu, sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts est l'habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts est l'habillage d'origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts הינה מעטפת ברירת המחדל של Kodi, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi, njegovim uklanjanjem može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts は Kodi のデフォルトスキンですので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts - это модернизированная обложка KODI</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts är standard skalet för Kodi, ta bort den kan orsaka problem</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Estuary v2 Extended Shortcuts 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<email>nkvoronov@gmail.com</email>
		<source>https://github.com/nkvoronov/skin.estuary2-extended.git</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-09.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-10.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-11.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-12.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-13.png</screenshot>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>
</addons>
